I got wasted cause I didn’t wanna deal with
myself tonight
My thoughts get drowned until I feel alright
I keep drinking til I’m someone I don’t
recognize
I got wasted
I got wasted cause I didn’t wanna deal with
myself tonight
My thoughts get drowned until I feel alright
I keep drinking til I’m someone I don’t
recognize
I got wasted
Repeat the cycle everyday I gotta start with
a drink
My life been getting sorta crazy and I don’t
wanna think
I look myself right in the mirror and I don’t
even blink
Then I get angry take the rest and pour it
right in the sink
I know where this road goes
alcohol ain’t my friend but i keep drinking
cause these demons roam and follow me round
everywhere I go
it clouds my mind and soul
it turns my heart cold
but I keep drinking cause it makes me feel
like I’m not alone
I having problems my pride won’t let me
reach out
Looking at this bottle having nothing but
doubt
Don’t wanna drink but it keeps coming around
and around and around
I got wasted cause I didn’t wanna deal with
myself tonight
My thoughts get drowned until I feel alright
I keep drinking til I’m someone I don’t
recognize
I got wasted
I got wasted cause I didn’t wanna deal with
myself tonight
My thoughts get drowned until I feel alright
I keep drinking til I’m someone I don’t
recognize
I got wasted
I know I need to quit
I gotta do better
Example to these kids
Cause they’re watching when I’m there
But I’m scared
Cause I been chasing the man that I am when
I start to drink
He’s cocky confident and he don’t give
a damn what you think
This world is beating me down and it’s
pushed me right to brink
I take a shot every time because man it helps
me escape
I’m taking care of these people but no one
takes care of me
I want to talk to somebody but I feel no one
relates
I need I better now
I think I’ve lost my way
I’m having battles with faith
It’s painted right on my face
I hope better times are coming
No chase but I’m still running
I gotta take control
And I won’t stop for nothing
Dear God this is my test
Promise that I’ll do my best
Just help with this pain I feel and pressure
that is on my chest
I got wasted cause I didn’t wanna deal with
myself tonight
My thoughts get drowned until I feel alright
I keep drinking til I’m someone I don’t
recognize
I got wasted
I got wasted cause I didn’t wanna deal with
myself tonight
My thoughts get drowned until I feel alright
I keep drinking til I’m someone I don’t
recognize
I got wasted